Put me down. I can manage on my own.
Your foot hasn't healed yet. Don't push yourself.
Thank you for tonight.
Remember to apply the ointment when you get back.
Rest up for the next few days.
Okay.
What about your family?
I'll go back when my dad sorts things out.
Okay.
We're here.
I'm heading in.
Yin Zixi.
Yes?
I like you.
What did you say?
Nothing.
Be careful going upstairs.
Okay.
Do you know who ordered this?
I don't know.
I just heard someone wants to make trouble for Yin Zixi,
but they didn't contact anyone inside the student council.
Let me know if you find any clues.
Okay.
What exactly did he want to say then?
I accidentally sprained my ankle during the photoshoot today.
Thankfully An Yufan was there.
I hope I didn't take up too much of his time.
Xixi,
did you read the tips I gave you?
I finished it.
Then why haven't I seen you stream?
I'm still preparing.
Still preparing?
You can't miss this opportunity.
Mom, I don't even have a place to stream.
Can't you just do it in your dorm?
No.
Streaming at school isn't that simple.
Xixi,
isn't Yin Zixi doing a great job?
Don't waste my efforts, okay?
I'm not like her.
She has a sugar daddy pushing her up the ranks,
and a senior giving her backstage support.
How can I do it when I have nothing?
You build it up as you go.
How will you know if it works if you don't try?
Maybe resources will come as you stream.
I will help you too,
sweetie.
I also found a batch of new designer clothes.
If you stream with these clothes...
As a style reflecting the form of news,
Wow.
Look at this.
it mainly includes news, communications, news features, and exclusive interviews.
News is presented in the most direct and concise way.
Who did this?
Is it true?
There are even photos.
I didn't expect her to be like this.
Well, she is an internet celebrity.
What's wrong?
What is this?
What do you want?
This is the card I found at the scene where Yin Zixi was kidnapped.
Did you arrange it?
What does an internet cafe have to do with me?
Stop playing dumb.
The off-campus esports competitions every year,
aren't they all organized by you?
Even if it does,
what can a business card prove?
If you dare touch Yin Zixi,
don't blame me for not being polite.
Let's begin.
Yes, President.
I understand.
Do it.
What are you doing?
Those are my things.
We received a complaint
saying you're doing illegal live streaming here.
The student union has demanded an investigation into you.
That's a rumor.
Can you judge right and wrong based on just one picture?
I don't care about that.
You are now required to stop the startup project here.
Continue.
Stop! Let go of my stuff!
Qianqian.
Isn't Yin Zixi doing well?
Don't waste Mom's good intentions, okay?
What are you doing?
I might have to live stream in the dorm from now on.
Then your dorm is fine, isn't it?
No.
Yin Zixi, the equipment can't be moved back to the dorm.
Why?
There won't be enough space in the dorm.
No, there will be.
Don't you have a live streaming room?
Why do you have to expand your business
to the dorm?
The student union won't let me use the previous venue anymore.
The dorm is already so small.
And you want to pile up so many things.
Don't you have top donators?
Why don't you ask them
to rent a bigger venue for you?
Yang Qian.
I really didn't expect you to see me this way too.
Hello.
Where are you?
Here.
What happened here?
The venue was taken back.
Can we move these
back to your apartment first?
I moved those clothes to the storage downstairs.
Was it the Student Union?
How about this.
Let's pause the live stream for now.
It's a good time for you to take a rest.
I'll go back and explain it clearly to the teacher
and see how to handle this matter.
I'm going to the restroom.
Yin Zixi.
I'll leave the towel on the cabinet.
I'm going out for a bit.
Assistant Casting Director Xi Chongjing
Props Assistant Li Kunxiao
Production Vehicle Yi Mingle
Yitong